http://uniformsandscrubs.com/privacy-policy

Group Orders
CollectionsPink RibbonDisneyVeterinaryDentalPediatricsCharacterHolidayBudgetNew ArrivalsSale ItemsClearance ItemsSolidsPrintsPantsJacketsLab CoatsLab Coats - ColorsDressesSkirtsVestsStudentsKidsMaternityTeesPolosWhitesChefwearSocksFootwearStethoscopesLandauUrbaneSmittenScrub ZoneBarcoGrey's AnatomyCherokeeCherokee WorkwearDickiesDanskoWhite SwanJockey ScrubsMETA LabwearLandau FootwearRxSkechersAMPS SocksFive Star ChefwearPeachesMed CoutureKoi ScrubsOrange StandardLittmann®PrimaLabcoats by BarcoStapled ClogsXPWaldenMed-ManDisneyTooniformsScrub HQFusionFlexiblesCarharttFour-StretchOriginsWonderFLEXWonderWinkAccessoriesGen FlexXtreme StretchEDSBarrierBio StretchHeartsoulWorkFlow - CLEARANCEEasy FitFundamentalsCode Happy - CLEARANCEInfinityAntimicrobialMC²Cross-FlexSapphireWonderWink WonderWorkLuxeMaevnWW Flex - CLEARANCESapphire Cherokee - CLEARANCELynx - CLEARANCEGA SignatureGA ActiveCareismaActivateBarco OneEONRed PandaEssenceKoi LIteAll DayPerformance RXRockwallWorkwear RevolutionDynamixGA ImpactWorkwear ProfessionalsiFlexLandau Pre-WashedUrbane UltimateUrbane PerformanceSmitten BlushBarco One WellnessGA StretchWorkwear Core StretchEDS EssentialsAdvanceEDS SignaturesLandau ProFlexGA EdgeWonderWink AeroWonderWink PROWonderWink W123TouchEnergySignatureBarco MotionPPEHanesFormPPE - MasksRev TechDickies RetroDickies Balance
Products
Scrubs
Scrub Tops
Scrub Pants
Scrub Jackets
Lab Coats
Dresses
Skirts
UniformsAndScrubs.com Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how UniformsAndScrubs.com collects information from all end users of UniformsAndScrubs.com' internet services (the "Services") — those who access some of our Services but do not make a purchase ("Visitors") as well as those who make a purchase ("Customers") — what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. UniformsAndScrubs.com requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Introduction
UniformsAndScrubs.com collects information in different ways from Visitors and customers who access the various parts of our Services. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.
What We Collect
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What We Do with the Information We Gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer e-gift cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a e-gift card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
When Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to UniformsAndScrubs.com, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. UniformsAndScrubs.com does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.
From time to time we will use the email addresses in our customer database to inform and provide offers to our visitors and customers about related products and/or specials that may be interesting and useful.  We will never provide this information to any outside party and greatly limit this type of use.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. The information you provide—including credit card information—is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers.  Our cart is a Magento site which is one of the world's largest providers of secure e-commerce solutions (http://www.magentocommerce.com/), and is hosted by AWS, the benchmark of cloud service quality and security.  While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
Cookies" and How UniformsAndScrubs.com Uses Them
A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. UniformsAndScrubs.com may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our networks. If you are a Customer, we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services.  The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Special Cases
It is the policy of UniformsAndScrubs.com not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Customers in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to prohibit such unrelated uses. However, UniformsAndScrubs.com may disclose personal information about Visitors or Customers, if we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to operate the Services properly or to protect UniformsAndScrubs.com and our Members.
UniformsAndScrubs.com' Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws.
Revisions to This Policy
UniformsAndScrubs.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted here and will only apply to information collected after any such change.
Where to Direct Questions About the UniformsAndScrubs.com Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, contact us via telephone at 855-391-9200, or via email at questions@UniformsAndScrubs.com.
List of Cookies We Collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
